Student Voice, The; Collection ua950.013
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
The Student Voice Collection
1999-2006
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
ua950.013
0.50 cubic ft.
Collection is made up of the publication The Student Voice.
Historical Note
The student voice was as magazine published by the Student Association from 1999 to 2006. The publication discussed campus events, highlighted sporting events, faculty spotlights, and other news. The Voice was published on a semi monthly basis, very often with a summer edition be released.
Scope and Contents
This collection is made up of the publication The Student Voice dating from the years 1999 to 2006. The first number of the periodical from October 1999 is missing. There duplicates of many copies in the folders.
Arrangement of the Collection
Collection is arranged in chronological order.
Acquisition Information
All items in this collection were transferred to the University Libraries, M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections and Archives.
Access
Access to this record group is unrestricted.
College Publications; Student publications; UAlbany Student Groups
- The Student Voice Volume 1 Issue 1, 1999 October (Box 1, Folder 1)
- The Student Voice Volume 1 Issue 2, 1999 November (Box 1, Folder 2)
- The Student Voice Volume 1 Issue 3, 2000 February (Box 1, Folder 2)
- The Student Voice Volume 1 Issue 4, 2000 March (Box 1, Folder 2)
- The Student Voice Volume 1 Issue 5, 2000 April (Box 1, Folder 2)
- The Student Voice Volume 1 Issue 6, 2000 May (Box 1, Folder 3)
- The Student Voice Volume 2 Issue 1, 2000 October (Box 1, Folder 3)
- The Student Voice Volume 2 Issue 2, 2000 November (Box 1, Folder 3)
- The Student Voice Volume 2 Issue 3, 2000 December (Box 1, Folder 3)
- The Student Voice Volume 2 Issue 4, 2001 February (Box 1, Folder 4)
- The Student Voice Volume 2 Issue 5, 2001 April (Box 1, Folder 4)
- The Student Voice Volume 3 Issue 1, 2001 November (Box 1, Folder 4)
- The Student Voice Volume 3 Issue 2, 2001 December (Box 1, Folder 4)
- The Student Voice Volume 3 Issue 3, 2002 March (Box 1, Folder 5)
- The Student Voice Volume 4 Issue 3, 2002 December (Box 1, Folder 5)
- The Student Voice Volume 4 Issue 4, 2003 February (Box 1, Folder 5)
- The Student Voice Volume 4 Issue 5, 2003 March (Box 1, Folder 5)
- The Student Voice Volume 4 Issue 6, 2003 April (Box 1, Folder 6)
- The Student Voice Volume 4 Issue 7, 2003 May (Box 1, Folder 6)
- The Student Voice Volume 5 Issue 1, 2003 August (Box 1, Folder 6)
- The Student Voice Volume 5 Issue 2, 2003 September (Box 1, Folder 6)
- The Student Voice Volume 5 Issue 3, 2003 October (Box 1, Folder 7)
- The Student Voice Volume 5 Issue 4, 2003 November (Box 1, Folder 7)
- The Student Voice Volume 5 Issue 5, 2003 December (Box 1, Folder 7)
- The Student Voice Volume 5 Issue 6, 2004 February (Box 1, Folder 8)
- The Student Voice Volume 5 Issue 7, 2004 April (Box 1, Folder 8)
- The Student Voice Volume 6, 2004 August (Box 1, Folder 8)
- The Student Voice Volume 6, 2004 September (Box 1, Folder 8)
- The Student Voice Volume 6, 2004 October (Box 2, Folder 1)
- The Student Voice Volume 6, 2004 November (Box 2, Folder 1)
- The Student Voice Volume 6, 2005 February (Box 2, Folder 1)
- The Student Voice Volume 6, 2005 June (Box 2, Folder 1)
- The Student Voice Volume 7, 2005 September (Box 2, Folder 1)
- The Student Voice Volume 7, 2005 October (Box 2, Folder 2)
- The Student Voice Volume 7, 2005 November (Box 2, Folder 2)
- The Student Voice Volume 7, 2006 January (Box 2, Folder 2)
- The Student Voice Volume 7, 2006 February (Box 2, Folder 2)
- The Student Voice Volume 7, 2006 March (Box 2, Folder 3)
- The Student Voice Volume 7, 2006 April (Box 2, Folder 3)